Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.17 01:38:20
前季回顾
[narrator] Last season on Grey's Anatomy:
你该走了. 我要迟到了. 我说真的. 再见...
You have to go. l'm late. Seriously. Goodbye... uh...
- Derek. - 是的.
- Derek. - Yeah.
一个月以前你们在医学院，医生教你们.
A month ago you were in med school being taught by doctors.
现在你们是医生了.
- Today, you are the doctors. - [Bailey] You're interns. Grunts.
你们是实习医生, 新兵, 什么都不是 外科的食物链的最底层.
Nobodies. Bottom of the surgical food chain.
像糖果一样, 但是有血, 比糖果好多了.
lt's like candy, but with blood, which is so much better.
Shepherd医生在那里.
Dr. Shepherd? He's over there.
这里有谁觉得自己不知道在做什么?
[George] Who feels like they have no idea what they're doing?
- 别这样看着我. - 怎么样看了?
- Stop looking at me like that. - Like what?
像你看着我裸体一样.
Like you've seen me naked.
我不是因为和我老板睡觉才被选进外科的
l don't get picked 'cause l slept with my boss
我不是因为有一个有名的妈妈才进医学院的.
and didn't get into med school 'cause l have a famous mother.
我想我以前是一个医生.
l used to be a doctor, l think.
好吧,George 和Izzie, 你们可以搬进来了.
[Meredith] Fine, George and lzzie, you can move in.
你和我分手仅仅是因为一瓶tequila（龙舌兰酒）
[Derek] You blew me off for a bottle of tequila.
意识到真相真是没有什么好处.
lt's not nearly as much fun to wake up to.
你们不介意把车挪一下吧?
You mind movin' this tail wagon?
下次我再看到你以任何方式对Meredith Grey表示出好感,
The next time l see you favoring Meredith Grey in any way,
我保证让她一个月进不了手术室.
l'll make sure she doesn't see the inside of an OR for a month.
你要知道，我是你的上司.
- l'm your boss. - You don't scare me.
你不用吓我.
你应该知道 Richard 同时向我们两个人 承诺说要提拔我们当主任.
- Richard promised chief to both of us. - Keep friends close and enemies closer.
善待朋友，更要善待敌人.
早上好,模特医生.
- Morning, Dr. Model. - Dr. Evil Spawn.
恶魔之子医生.
You're not the enemy. You're just the competition.
你不是敌人.
你只是竞争对像.
我们在干吗?
What is this that we're doing here?
你需要弄清楚吗?
[Yang] You need a definition?
还有别的选择.
[Meredith] There are other options.
这个是肿瘤, 它压迫了你的视神经.
lt's a tumor. lt's pressing against your optic nerve.
你得梅毒了.
You've got syphilis.
我不知道是怎么得的.
[George] l don't know how this happened.
你和 Alex?
You and Alex?
你把梅毒传染给我的?!
You gave me syphilis?
有人说这个是艳情.
[Derek] Some people would call this a relationship.
- 谁? - 我.
- Who? - Me.
哦，我的天.
My God, you're falling for him.
你爱上他了
是什么能让一个好医生放弃优厚的待遇到西雅图来?
What makes a hotshot doc leave the Big Apple?
- 你好，我是Addison Shepherd. - Shepherd?
- Hi. l'm Addison Shepherd. - Shepherd?
你就是那个勾引我丈夫的女人吧.
You must be the woman who's been screwing my husband.
要成为一个好的外科大夫 你必须像外科大夫那样思考.
[Meredith] To be a good surgeon, you have to think like a surgeon.
情感是凌乱的.
Emotions are messy.
把它们整齐地藏好步入无菌室
Tuck them neatly away and step into a clean, sterile room
一个程序简单的地方...
where the procedure is simple.
切开,缝合,关上.
Cut, suture and close.
你看上去很眼熟.
You look familiar. You been here before?
你以前来过?
来过一次.
Once. That worked out really well.
这酒很管用.
只有两件事
l know that look. lt's one of two things.
你老板让你不爽,或者是你男朋友. 是哪个?
Either your boss is giving you hell or your boyfriend is. Which is it?
都是.
Both.
但是有时你要面对一个不会愈合的伤口
But sometimes, you're faced with a cut that won't heal.
我男朋友是我的老板, 这曾经是个问题.
My boyfriend is my boss, which was a problem.
但是比起我的男朋友有个老婆的事实还算不上什么.
But not as big a problem as the fact that my boyfriend has a wife.
告诉你吧,
Tell you what, this one, it's on the house.
这杯是免费的.
一个伤口的线开了,敞开着.
A cut that rips its stitches wide open.
Addison, 你在这里干嘛?
- What are you doing here? - Your hair's different.
你的发型变了.
- 很多事情都不一样了. - 比以前长了.我很喜欢,很像Russell Crowe.
- A lot of things are different. - lt's longer. lt's very Russell Crowe.
- 你在这里干嘛? - 你在这里干嘛?
- What are you doing here? - You just pick up and leave everything?
你把你拥有的都扔掉了
你的房子, 你的事业, 你的朋友?
Your house, your practice, your friends? You had a life in Manhattan.
- 在曼哈顿你曾经有你的生活. - 曾经.
现在你在西雅图有了个女友.
Had.
And now you have a girlfriend in Seattle.
她看起来... 很甜.
- She seems sweet. - The ice you're on. Thin.
你很...心虚.
她很年轻
She's young.
她睁着大大的眼睛, "哦, 他是个脑外医生" 事情就发生了
That wide-eyed, he's-a-brain-surgeon thing, but still sweet.
但还是很甜, 正是你期待的那样, 对吗?
Which was what you were going for. The anti-Addison?
反Addison?
lf you came to try to win me back, forget it.
你如果来这里是想重新得到我, 你休想
我是的. 我横跨全国飞过来去回忆
l did. l flew across the country to reminisce over wedding photos,
结婚照片, 醉酒, 跌在床上, 让你认识到你不能离开我.
get drunk, fall into bed, and make you realize you can't live without me.
放松,Derek.
Relax. Derek, l'm here for work.
我是来这里工作的.
l'm helming the TTTS case you guys admitted last week
我接管你们上周接受的T.T.T.S病例
- 根据Richard的简报,我应该是... - Richard 知道你来这里?
and from Richard's briefing...
- He knew you were coming? - He asked me. Didn't he say?
他让我来的.
- No. He didn't. - Hm. Surprise.
- 他没有告诉你? - 不，他没有.
惊讶吧.
这头发, 尽管...
The hair, though. You know l've always had a thing for Russell Crowe.
你知道我一直都喜欢Russell Crowe.
让我看看.
Let me see it.
没有伤口, 一般性肿胀.
No lacerations, minimal swelling.
George 真是把你揍得不轻
- George really knocked you around. - He's a lightweight.
那家伙是个轻量级.
- Could've pinned him in a second. - Why didn't you?
我想揍他马上就可以揍
是啊, 但是你为什么不揍呢?
Are you kidding? l'm riding a career in Plastics all the way to the bank.
你开玩笑吗?
我想当整形科医生.
损伤了我这对宝贝手我可担负不了
Can't afford to injure these babies.
特别是用在O'Malley这种人身上.
- Especially over O'Malley. - You had it coming.
你自找的.
The dude punches like my sister.
那家伙打人的力气像我妹妹一样.
哦,照你的说法, 你被一个女孩扁了?
So, by your definition then you got beat up by a girl.
[chuckles]
大家都来欢呼吧!
- All hail the champ! - [whooping]
这么说我们的Alex终于罪有应得了?
So my guy Alex finally got what was coming to him.
George一拳就把他打倒了.
- George knocked him down in one punch. - l don't want to talk about it!
你应该看看.
Brag, champ, brag! You've earned it!
我不想说这个了.
好好吹吹吧.应该的.
来瓶啤酒?
Can l have a beer, please?
咱们赌谁最倒霉吧.
Let's play a game of whose life sucks the most.
我会赢的.
- l'll win. l always win. - No, you don't want to play with me.
- 我总是赢. - 你不会想和我赌这个的
我就要赌.
Oh, l do. l'll even go first.
我还要第一个说.
Derek结过婚.
Derek's married.
George, 啤酒从你的鼻孔滴下来.
George, beer is dripping from your nostrils.
我说过我会赢.
- Told you l'd win. - No, you don't win.
不,你没有赢.
你听到我了没有?
Did you hear me? l said Derek is married.
我说Derek结过婚了.
As in pigheaded, adulterous, liar married.
这个猪头, 通奸的, 骗子是结过婚的.
你说什么都不可能超过这个了.
Nothing you could say could top that.
我怀孕了.
l'm pregnant.
我赢了.
l win.
Joe, 你没事吧?
- [groans] - [man] Joe, you all right?
- [smashing] - [man] Hey, Joe!
可能是Joe赢了.
OK. Maybe Joe wins.
Joe, 躺下.
- Lie down. - [man] The medics are coming.
你们叫警察了?
- You called the gurney patrol? - Sit back and relax.
坐好放松.
- The hospital will run some tests... - Tests? l don't need tests. l'm fine!
我们要把你送到医院做一些检查.
检查? 不. 我不需要任何检查,我很好.
You collapsed! On the floor. lt's your bar. You know how filthy this floor is.
伙计,你瘫倒在地板上了.
这你的酒吧.你知道这里的地板有多脏.
- 脉博有力. - 小范围颅骨挫伤.
- Pulse is strong. - Minor skull contusions.
- 你和人上床了? - 什么? 谁?
- You're sleeping with someone? - What?
这有什么奇怪的? george都有做这种事.
- Even George got some action. - Correction. George got some syphilis.
没错. George 得梅毒了.
- How could l not know? - Forget this.
你和别人上床了我怎么不知道?
算了吧. 医院就在路对面.
The hospital is right across the street.
我怎么都相信我能自己走到马路对面.
l can sure as hell walk across the street by myself.
-我想我们应该... -不，我来吧. Joe!
- l think we should... - No, l got him. Joe!
好吧,详细一点.
All right.
Details. You're pregnant?
你怀孕了?
What are you gonna do?
你打算怎么办?
Look, you know what happens to pregnant interns.
你知道实习生怀孕了会怎么样.
我可不要去妇科或者整天和丘疹打交道
l'm not switching to the vagina squad or spending my life popping zits.
我太有天赋了.
l'm too talented. Surgery's my life.
外科是我的生活.
Which begs the question: Who are you sleeping with?
- 别回避话题, 你和谁上床了? - 一个男的.
就这些？
- Just a guy. - That's all l get?
- 你不能把这个事情告诉我了又想让我不管. - 那就盯着我吧.
You can't just bring something like this up and expect me to drop it.
Well, watch me.
你今天晚上怎么回来了?
Don't you have a date with McDreamy?
- 你不是在和梦幻麦克约会吗? - 大概是已婚麦克吧.
- More like McMarried. - McWhat?
麦克什么?
l came to check on Joe.
我来看看Joe.
- You think he's gonna be OK? - Will he need an operation?
你认为他应该会没有事吧?
你觉得他需要手术吗?
[Derek] Operation, yes. OK, hard to tell.
手术... 是的.
不太好说.
Basilar artery's like a balloon. Subarachnoid bleeding.
基底动脉涨的像气球一样, 蛛网膜下腔出血
动脉瘤想高尔夫球一样大.
- Aneurysm the size of a golf ball. - No way to clip something like that.
没有办法用血管钳夹住它.
- Not without magic fingers. - Or a standstill operation.
除非有魔术手指.
或者是静止手术.
You're doing a standstill... He's doing a standstill operation.
你要做静止手术... 他要做静止手术.
我想试试.
l'd like to try. First l need some additional patient history,
但是首先我需要一些病例资料, 通宵实验室和脑部诊断.
overnight labs, and a cerebral angio.
我喝醉了.
- l'm drunk. - [Derek] Meredith...
Meredith...
混蛋麦克.
[lzzie, softly] McBastard.
Ahem.
你在干嘛？
- What are you doing? - Uh...
我站在她一边, 但是我们在讨论静止手术的可能性.
l am on her side. But we're talking a possible standstill here.
考虑.
Recognize.
Meredith.
- Meredith! - Go away!
- 走开. - 等下.
Just wait. We should discuss this.
我们需要谈谈
Here's a thought. No! Quit following me!
我有一个想法.
不. 别跟着我.
- At least let me explain. - Explain?
听我解释下好吧.
解释? 你知道应该什么时候解释吗?
You should have explained the night we met in the bar.
我们在酒吧里见到的晚上 在任何事情发生以前.
Before any of the rest of it.
是的，那时解释才是合适的.
- That would have been a good time. - Look, l know how you feel.
我知道你的感觉.
Do you? Somehow l doubt that.
你知道?
我才不相信.
Because if you did, you would shut up,
如果你知道, 你应该闭嘴 转身回去,
and you would turn around and go back inside,
你应该知道我马上就要进我的车里
because you would realize that l am this close to getting in my car
我会在停车场把你撞倒!
and running you down in the parking lot!
给我钥匙.
- Where're your keys? - l'm fine!
- 我很好. - Meredith, 给我钥匙.
Meredith, give me your keys.
咱们走，好吗?
[George] Let's go home.
[man and woman laugh]
这个丈夫是最差劲的.
- ...and the husband was the... - [Richard laughs]
[clears throat]
[sighs, clears throat]
我早上回来再汇报我的工作
Well, l will be back in the morning to report for duty.
你休息一下.
And you... get some rest.
她在这里干嘛?
What is she doing here?
你我都知道她在她的领域里是最强的.
You and l both know she's the best in the field.
引进Addie是医院的决定,没有私情
Bringing Addie out was a business decision, nothing personal.
多么轻松的事啊.
Oh, well, what a relief.
这个不是私事.
lt's not personal. lt is personal to me.
这对我来说是私事.
The workings of my surgical unit don't have any...
在我的手术组里工作
-别弄出任何事情... -别把我老婆搅和进去!
- Don't include my wife! - Don't include your private life!
别把你的私生活弄进去.
Burke会代理主任直到我回来.
Burke will act as chief of surgery until l'm back on my feet.
你让Burke当主任?
You gave chief to Burke.
我说过,要成为主任医师就不要闹私人情绪.
There's no room for personal in being chief.
你这么说是什么意思?
- What is that supposed to mean? - You have been sleeping with an intern.
你和实习生上床有多长时间了?
[chuckles]
我猜成为主任并不是完全没是有私情的
So l guess part of being chief is personal.
你出去的时候把门关上.
Close the door on your way out.
Allis.
L.S.
[woman on PA] IV nurse call ICU, extension 323.
Babcock.
IV nurse call ICU, extension 323.
直角钳.
Right-angle clamp.
我弄完了会消毒的.
Oh. l'm gonna sterilize everything when l'm done.
器械护士都不会知道我在这里.
The scrub nurses won't know l was here.
我守口如瓶.
My lips are sealed.
Dr. Tucker to Radiology. Dr. Tucker to Radiology.
我有一个问题要问.
So, l have a question to ask.
我看了时间安排，咱们两个今天晚上都不用值班
l checked the schedule and l noticed that you and l are both off tonight.
我为晚餐预订了位置.
l made reservations.
一个我很喜欢的餐馆.
l have a favorite restaurant.
这些都不算是问题.
None of those were questions.
你愿意今天晚上和我出去吃饭吗?
Would you like to go out to dinner with me tonight?
手术室是我唯一可以去的和思考的地方..
You know, the OR is the one place where l can come and think.
我现在正在思考，行不行？
l'm thinking right now, OK?
好吧.
Of course.
[metal scrapes]
我明白了.
l get it.
我不是一个暴力的人.
l'm not a violent person. l'm a pacifist.
我是个和平主义者, 但是, 你知道
But, you know, he just kept pushing and push...
他不停的弄我
He pushed me, l pushed back.
他弄我, 我也返过来弄他.
l was pushed. And now he...
我被他弄,而他现在
你知道吗? Alex 再想把你怎么样，就告诉我
lf Alex tries to lay a hand on you, just tell me, l'll take care of it.
我会处理的.
You... [laughs]
我不需要你...
l don't need you to take care of it.
管这件事.
lf Alex starts something l'll handle it myself.
如果Alex来找事，我自己解决.
我能处理.
l can handle it.
好了大伙，有任务了.
OK, people, assignments.
Yang,你今天休息.
Yang, you're on discharges. O'Malley report to room E1 9.
O'Malley,到E19房报道.
Grey come see me, and who was on call last night?
Grey,来见我,昨天晚上谁值班?
邋遢, 邋遢,邋遢.
Sloppy, sloppy, sloppy.
- 重新做这些然后午饭前把它们给我, 明白吗? - 明白.
Redo these and return them to me before lunch, understood?
Karev,别试我.
- Understood. - Karev, don't tempt me.
有人受欢迎.
- Somebody's popular. - Meaning?
什么意思?
There's been a special request, just for you.
有一个对你的特别要求.
这些主任医师全都要管?
[Burke] The chief runs through all of this?
在午饭前.
Before lunch. After, you've got calls to return, a budget to approve,
然后, 你要回电话, 批准预算,
两个员工会议,四个Richard的手术, 包括你的.
two staff meetings, and four of Richard's surgeries, including your own.
没有问题.
Absolutely. No problem.
新手...
[chuckles] Virgins.
祝贺词都到位了.
So. Congratulations are in order.
别吓我了, Shepherd. 我就当你的老板几天.
Don't sweat it, l'll only be your boss for a few days.
我很了解Richard的康复时间.
l'm aware of Richard's recovery time. l operated on him, remember?
我给他做的手术，不记得了?
我记得.
l do. He survived and chose me to take over while recruiting your wife.
你给他做手术,他手术后选我代理他 还雇用你老婆
很清楚，他脑子有毛病.
Clearly, he has brain damage.
还是你的前妻?
Or is it your ex-wife? l'm a little fuzzy on that.
我在弄不清这个事情.
- We're separated. - Sorry to interrupt, Dr. Burke.
我们分居了.
对不起打扰了,Burke医生.
- 没关系. - 她总是很烦人.
- You're never interrupting. - She always is.
我正在查看
l was checking to see if Dr. Burke secured the intern...
- Burke是否提供了 - 你要的实习生.
The intern you requested? He did.
他提供了.
T.T.T.S的定义.
[Addison] Define TTTS.
双胞胎输血综合症, 连在一起的孪生双胞胎.
Twin-twin transfusion syndrome. Conjoined fetal twins.
通过什么连接?
Connected by?
胎盘内的血管.
- Blood vessels in the placenta. - Meaning?
意味着?
一个胎儿得到的血太多了, 另一个太少了 两人都有生命危险.
One twin gets too much blood, the other too little, endangering both.
我本以为你知道, Grey.
l'd expect you to know that, Grey.
你告诉我治愈的机会不多，但是...
You said probably nothing could be done.
T.T.T.S.一般无法治愈, 除非你是世界上某些极少数的
TTTS is usually impossible to correct.
Unless you are one of a handful of surgeons in the world
知道怎么分离胎儿血管的医生， 你很幸运, 我会.
who knows how to separate fetal blood vessels.
Which, luckily for you, l am.
所有你明天就可以手术.
So we'll get you into surgery tomorrow.
如果你还有什么问题,就问Grey医生.
lf you have any questions at all, please ask Dr. Grey.
在我看来, 她是本医院最受欢迎的实习医生.
From what l have seen, she is one of the hospital's most popular interns.
如果你给我机会，我能回答你问我的问题
l could've answered your question given a chance.
闭嘴, Grey.
Chin up. l'm this tough on everyone, not just the women my husband sleeps with.
我对谁都不好, 不仅仅是对和我丈夫上过床的女人.
预约B超...
Order an ultrasound for her and pre-op labs in...
我能看看E19的病例吗?
Hi. Can l have the chart for E1 9, please? Thank you.
谢谢.
好的，你来了
Oh, good, you're here. Let's get started.
- 咱们开始吧. - 好吧.
OK.
- O'Malley?
- O'Malley. - Yeah?
- 你碰我了. - 是的
- You're touching me. - Yeah.
不要.
No. Carmen...
Carmen...
我想让你认真地听我说.
l want you to listen to me very carefully.
自从我来这里, 我不知道我的医生们 病人们、医院怎么了.
As long as l'm in here, l don't know what's happening out there.
With my doctors. My patients. My hospital.
你现在是我的耳目.
You are my eyes today. My ears.
我想让你当我的内探.
- l want you to be a sponge. - A sponge?
内探?
You report any and everything happening in this hospital to me.
你向我报告这个医院里面发生的任何事情
我是个调查内探.
- l'm an investigative sponge. - l'm not fooling around.
我不是瞎搅和的, O'Malley.
There's too much been happening lately under my radar.
我感觉最近发生了不少事情.
这样的情况不能再发生了.
lt stops today.
[woman on PA] IV nurse, call ICU extension 323 1.
IV nurse, call ICU extension 323 1.
Burke, 你把Grey交给Addison了?
Burke. You gave Grey to Addison. Are you sure about that?
你确定吗?
That's not your call, Shepherd. And for the record, l'm always sure.
那不是你能决定的, Shepherd.
对于记录, 我总是很确信.
你需要我做什么吗?
Did you need me? As the new chief, l'm...
- 因为我是新主任, 我是... - 临时主任.
- lnterim chief. - ''Chief' nonetheless.
尽管是主任.
Ever attempt a standstill surgery?
试过静止手术吗?
主要是因为动脉瘤的位置让手术变得很难.
[Derek] lt's the location of the aneurysm that makes it tricky.
你的体温会降得很低来，你不会受损伤 但你的心跳会停止.
Your body temperature would be lowered to protect it and stop the heart.
脑部血流停止, 降低动脉瘤破裂的危险.
Which stops blood flow to the brain which reduces the risk of rupture.
我有45分钟来夹住动脉瘤
l'll have 45 minutes to clip the aneurysm.
然后我再让心脏复跳.
- Before l get the heart started again. - You wanna freeze my body,
你想冷冻我的身体，抽干我的血 停跳我的心脏？
- drain my blood, and stop my heart? - And bring you back.
然后再让我复苏.
- ln under 45 minutes? - [Derek] Right.
在45分钟以内.
如果你超时了，能免费吗?
- lf you go over, is it free? - No.
不能.
Dr. Yang, you can go and handle the pre-op labs now.
杨大夫,你可以去做术前检查了.
多少钱?
How much? How much does something like this cost?
这种手术一般要花多少钱?
[Derek] Don't worry about that right now.
我觉得你现在最好不要担心.
你们说你能把我杀了然后救活我
Look, you guys say that you can kill me and bring me back, l believe you.
我相信你，你们是医生
You're doctors, but l own a bar.
但是我有一个酒吧.
l don't got any insurance so l'm not that concerned about the surgery
我没有医疗保险, 所以我不是那么关心手术
只要我能活着.
so much as what l'm gonna do when l survive it.
你给我个数
l need a number. Ten grand? Twenty?
1万? 2万?
3万?
- Thirty? - lt's a couple hundred at least.
至少要好几十万吧.
At least.
至少.
谁是Halloran?
[Alex] Who's Halloran?
4115房间的病号.
Patient in 41 1 5.
- [woman on PA] Dr. Cole, call the OR. - Red hair?
红头发?
Wife knits all the time? He had the colectomy?
夫妻关系良好?
他做了结肠切除术?
Ah, colon dude. That's right. Who's Monterroso?
花花肠子，是的.
谁是Monterosso?
4238. Mom with the really cute kids.
4238. 有两个可爱孩子的妈妈.
她昨晚体温骤升.
She spiked a post-op fever. You spent two hours with her.
- 你花了两个小时观察她. - 疝气.
Hernia chick. That's right.
你上周一直在治这些人.
You've treated them for a week and you don't know their names?
你怎么都知道他们的名字?
ln Surgery we don't waste time getting to know the patients.
外科是唯一一个不用浪费时间了解病人的专业.
- 他们是一大块肉, 我们是屠夫. - 他们是人.
- They're meat, we're butchers. - They're humans.
你知道人是什么,
You do know what a human is, Evil Spawn?
- 不是吗, 恶魔之子? - 我不是魔鬼.
l'm not evil. Unless evil turns you on.
除非魔鬼把你开启了.
你有没有早晨醒来，感觉到没有人喜欢你 我不知道你关不关心这个
Do you ever wake up, realize nobody likes you, and, l don't know, care?
Oh. [chuckles] l think somebody likes me.
我想有人喜欢我.
[Yang] Hey.
你当了主任就不说话了,嗨,Burke!
What, you don't speak now you're chief? Burke!
你想要什么?
- What do you want? - What?
什么?
What do you want? You don't want to go out to dinner.
你想要什么?
你不想出去吃饭.
You don't want to meet me in the on-call room, and you don't want to talk to me.
你不想在值班室见我， 肯定是你不想和我说话
我可以装着我知道,但是, 我连你家电话号码都没有.
l could pretend l know, but l don't have your home phone number.
告诉我，你到底想要什么?!
- So tell me, what do you want? - Don't yell at me.
别对我吼.
- 我们在这里说话的. - 你想干吗?
- We're having a conversation. - What do you want?
我不知道！
l don't know!
自己想想.
Figure it out.
今天有什么报告?
What's the report?
没有报告.
No report. lt's very quiet today, sir.
今天没有什么事情发生.
There's no gossip? Surgeries l should know about?
没有新闻, 闲话,手术吗？我都想知道?
得了,嚷嚷什么,O'Malley?
- Now come on, what's the buzz? - You know, not in halls, not in OR.
大厅里没事，手术室里没事, 楼梯间也没事.
Not in the stairwells.
特别是，你知道。没有事情发生在...
Especially nothing happening in the, you know... They're just stairwells.
只是楼梯间而已.
[Alex wolf whistles]
他们说你穿着女睡衣, 但是我想自己来看看.
They told me you were in a nightgown, but l thought l'd come see.
不错.
Very nice, huh.
听说O'Malley扁了你.漂亮的眼睛.
Heard O'Malley laid you out cold. Nice eye.
谁送来的?
- Whoa, who sent that? - We all pitched in. The whole floor.
我们都在内.
Well, please, tell the whole floor a big thank you.
整层楼的人.
谢谢整层楼的人
好的我会的.
Yeah, l will.
Alex,你一定要把我弄出去.
Alex, you gotta get me out of here, man. Get me transferred to County Hospital.
把我转到县医院或者别的医院.
Not County. Here, they can kill you and bring you back,
你可别去县里.
我的意思是说 这里他们知道怎么让你心跳停止然后复苏
but at County, they can just kill you. No joke.
但是县医院只知道怎么让你心跳停止 不是开玩笑
我花不起钱啊.
l can't afford this place, man. l'm gonna lose the bar.
我会失去酒吧的.
- Hey, Joe, how you doing? - Hey, Scooter.
Joe, 你好吗?
Scooter.
好了.那是我的.
OK. That's mine?
重要的事情先来.
- We'll start by saving your life. - The bar is my life. You know that.
我们要从救命开始.
这个酒吧是我的命啊.
You've been at last call every night since you moved here.
你知道的.至少你可以让我随叫随到 ，你搬到这里的每天晚上都可以.
我现在要把它关掉或者卖掉.
l'm gonna have to shut it down or sell it.
你不能这样做.
You can't do that. Place is an institution.
那个地方是公共机构.
l've owned the bar across the street for 1 4 years,
我拥有街对面的酒吧14年了,
到现在我还没有来过一次医院
and l've never been inside this hospital till now.
我现在把我的钱付了?
l'll pay my tab. That's gotta be good for something. How much is it?
这样还不错
多少钱?
Close to a grand.
快一千了.
你看60块怎么样...
How about l pay, like, 60?
这不错了.
That's good. And l'll pay you back later.
剩下的以后再还你.
担心鬼!
Hey, champ!
[PA] Orderly, please report to station three. Orderly, report to station three.
偷别人的丈夫会怎么样?
What does it take to go after another woman's husband?
什么意思?
- Excuse me? - lt happened to me.
我在说我.
Jeff moved in with a long-legged miniskirt who answers his phones
Jeff和一个长腿的穿超短裙的女人同居了 我怀孕3周了都是她替我丈夫接的电话
three weeks into my pregnancy. That gel is really cold.
顺便说下这个凝胶太凉了.
l'm sorry. l'm sorry about your husband.
很抱歉，我是说关于你的丈夫.
你对Montgomery Shepherd医生的丈夫抱歉吗?
Are you sorry about Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd's husband?
我今天要给你做一些检查.
l'm going to be checking a few things today.
我想是她要求和你一起工作的.
l bet she asked to work with you. lt's what l would have done.
这个是我将要做完的.
l'm gonna go check on your labs.
我要去给你做一些实验室检查.
[steady beeping]
[retches]
[flushing]
你好,阳光.
Heya, sunshine.
深呼吸.
Deep breath.
早孕晨吐真不爽.
Morning sickness must suck.
我们说清楚
Just so we're clear,
昨天晚上你听到的东西要只字不提
do not breathe a word of what you heard last night to anyone.
不许说我，不许说Meredith, 不许说Meredith和梦幻麦克医生.
Not about me. Not about Meredith. Not about Meredith and Dr. McDreamy...
你好,Burke医生.
- Hey, Dr. Burke. - Joe.
Joe.
昨晚生命体征平稳.
Um, vital signs stable overnight. Today's CT shows no re-bleeding.
今天CT提示没有新出血.
The EKG...
心电图...
提示...
shows...
um, normal sinus rhythm.
正常窦性心律.
No ischemia, no dysrhythmias.
无缺血, 无心律失常.
看来不错.
Looking good. Page me if there are any changes.
有变化叫我.
嗨，主任.
- [baby wails] - [George] Oh, hi, Chief.
没有，没有什么事情发生
No, not much going on.
除了你的临时主任和我的朋友在楼梯间里约会的事。
Other than your interim chief making out with my friend in the stairwell,
但是,内探的工作真恶心.
but, hey... Sponge duty sucks.
自言自语呢?
- You talking to yourself now? - Yes. No!
是的，不是!
糟糕. 我是一个差劲的内探, 漏消息的内探.
Damn it, l'm a bad sponge. A leaky sponge.
我会把所有糟糕的秘密都漏了的 我是一个差劲的骗子
l'm gonna leak all the wrong secrets.
l'm a bad liar, can't even lie about talking to myself.
我连在自言自语都不会撒谎.
你今天看上去不错.
You look nice today.
我用了新的唇膏.
Wore my new lip gloss
因为我前男友的妻子看起来像 Isabella freakin' Rossellini,我像我...自己.
'cause my ex-boyfriend's wife looks like lsabella freakin' Rossellini,
and l'm like... me.
我试着超过她，当她在这儿充当受害者时.
l'm trying to outdo her when she's the victim here. How crazy is that?
这样想好疯狂啊?
Not crazy. Smart.
不是疯，是聪明
You know, gloss, you know, prevents chapped lips and... you...
唇膏，预防嘴唇和...
前男友...不裂开?
Ex-boyfriend?
我是个邪恶的情妇.
l'm an evil mistress.
不过，你看上去不错.
Well, still. You look nice.
谢谢.
Thanks. What are you doing here?
你在这里干吗?
[stutters]
- 哦... - 别了, O'Malley. 说出来吧.
Come on, O'Malley. Out with it.
你能想像为什么Cristina 吻Burke吗?
OK. Can you think of any reason, any reason at all, really,
why Cristina would be kissing Burke?
[elevator bell]
到现在了，你还在警告我不要和老板上床吗,
After all this time. All your warnings about me sleeping with my boss,
- 你恰恰在做同样的事情? - 不一样.
- and you're doing the same thing? - lt's not the same.
- 一模一样! - 你和梦幻麦克确立关系了.
- lt's the same... - You two are in a relationship.
you和Burke在... 瑞士
And you and Burke are in?
Switzerland. lt's very neutral there. And they make very nice watches.
那里很中立.做的手表也很好.
你是不是连怀孕的事情都不想给他说?
Have you even bothered to tell Burke about the baby?
你和他说吗?
- Are you going to? - Look, Meredith, can we not go there?
Meredith,咱们能不能不说这个
你就不能让有事情
Can everyone just accept that l like to keep some things to myself?
只有我自己知道, 我不想把任何事都讨论到死
- l don't discuss everything to death. - Well, why even confide in me at all
你那么不想谈论这个事情为什么还要告诉我呢?
if you're so intent on not discussing it?
为什么还要告诉我?
Why even tell me?
当我发现了那个穿超短裙的女人 我给她打电话请她吃饭,
When l found out about the miniskirt, l called her up and took her to lunch.
瞧这多文明啊.
lt was perfectly civil. l said l didn't hold it against her,
我说我不是要和她作对, 既然事情发生了.
但是，真的，我只想给这个婊子点脸色看看 她让我老公放弃了15年的婚姻
that these things happened. But, really?
l wanted to put a face on the bitch
that got my husband to throw away 1 5 years of marriage.
有空吗?
- Got a second? - Depends on what you need.
看你需要什么了.
Who the hell is Dr. McDreamy?
到底谁是梦幻麦克医生?
我.我是梦幻麦克医生.
Me. l'm Dr. McDreamy.
我又高又帅.
l'm tall, handsome.
我喜欢找麻烦, 思考约会美女的困难.
l lean against things and ponder the difficulties of dating beautiful women.
我想在这里当外科大夫.
l'm trying to be a surgeon here!
- 找Meredith需要很大的勇气. - 得了，她有很好的推荐材料.
- That took a lot of nerve. - She came highly recommended.
-是的. -那么你不推荐她?
- Right. - So you don't recommend her?
- 不，我没有这样说. - 不仅仅是应为她的医疗技术.
- l did not say that. - Just not her medical skills.
你闭嘴好吗?
- Dr. Shepherd. - [both] Yes?
- Shepherd医生? - 嗯.
Labs confirm what look like abnormalities on the ultrasound.
实验室检查证实了超声上看到的畸形.
我想你应该来自己看看.
- l think you should come and see. - Fine. Let's go.
好.咱们走.
- Meredith. Meredith. - 别.
- Meredith. Meredith... - Don't.
[PA] Any available IV nurse to OR Two. Any available IV nurse to OR Two.
没有消息.
Well, no report.
是的,没有报告,像前一段一样.
You know, same nothing as earlier.
我该走了.
l should go.
事实上,有些事情,先生.
Oh, actually there is something, sir.
Burke和Shepherd在操场上划界?
- Burke and Shepherd marking territory? - No, sir.
不是.
lt's about Joe. The bartender.
是关于Joe，那个酒吧老板 他们静止手术的病人
The standstill patient.
看到了?
See. Bilateral pleural effusion with evidence of subQ edema.
双肋膜渗出,有皮下水肿.
说英语好吗?
ln English, please?
我们检查到婴儿看起来有早期心衰的征象.
We've detected what looks like beginning heart failure in the twins.
别害怕.
- Don't be alarmed. - Are my babies gonna be OK?
我的孩子会没事吗?
l'm going to take you into surgery now. Book the OR.
我马上要给你做手术. 不能等了,预定手术室,走!
Move.
让Pete每天晚上冲洗水管
[Joe] Tell Pete to wash out the taps every night. Not every other night.
不是隔一天一次,是一天一次.
And remind him that the delivery truck comes at 6:00a.m. Kegs go in the back.
提醒他送货车每天早晨6点到,小桶在后面.
还有一件事,
Oh, another thing. There's petty cash on the top shelf in the storage closet.
零钱在储藏柜最上面的架子上
我们只给病人做手术.
We're operating on patients. That's it.
- 我知道,但是... - 我很同情.真的
- l know, but... - l sympathize. l do.
但是解决Joe的经济问题不是我管的
But solving Joe's finances is not my job, it's not your job,
这也不是你的事情 我也确定这不是我今天给你分配的任务.
and it's sure as hell not the job l assigned you today.
把他切开、缝起来就不管了是不对的 他什么都没有剩下了.
lt seems wrong to cut him open, sew him up, and leave him, left with nothing.
如果我们能救他的命, 我们不可能让他一无所有
lf we can save his life, we'll hardly be leaving him with nothing.
[steady beeping]
这是所有我能做的.
That's as far as l can go for now. Let's start cooling him.
开始给他降温.
从后面看不到什么东西的, O'Malley.
Can't see much from back here, O'Malley.
我知道.我正在找一个能帮助Joe的缺口.
l know. l'm trying to find a loophole to help Joe.
你认识Joe吗?
- [George] You know Joe? - Oh, yeah.
那年我是这里唯一的一个女实习生
l was the only female intern my year.
我谁都不认识, 除了Joe也没有人认识我.
l didn't know anybody and nobody knew me except Joe.
他了解我.
He knew me.
你和Joe...
Oh. So, you and Joe?
你这种人想的事情就是怎样和人上床.
All you people ever think about is how to get into somebody's pants.
你真恶心.
You're nasty. That's why you got syphilis.
所以你得了梅毒.
Joe was the first person here to say l'd make a good surgeon.
Joe是这里第一个告诉我我可以当个好的外科大夫的人 不是你想的那些东西
Not that he knew anything about it. But it was somethin' when l had nothin'.
但是这对什么都没有的我来说可是一件大事.
是的,我是铁石心肠的人, 你带来了点心.
Oh, sure. l'm the guy with the heart of stone and you brought snacks.
这个是工作餐.
- lt's a working lunch. - Snacks to watch Joe die.
吃着点心看着Joe死.
He's not gonna ''die'' die. They'll bring him back.
他不会死翘翘的.他们能给他弄回来.
他要体验一次死,没有脉搏.
He is going to ''die'' die. No ''pulse'' pulse. He'll be ''dead'' dead.
他会死翘翘的.
lt's a granola bar, Alex.
这是格兰诺拉麦片饼干，不是一包 看电影时吃的巧克力薄荷糖和爆米花
Not a bag of supersize popcorn and a box of chocolate movie mints.
对了.
That's it.
死了.
Dead!
不好意思.
Excuse me.
Julie我们要给你做宫腔镜.
[Addison] Julie, we're gonna go in laparoscopically.
你不会有感觉的.
You're not gonna feel anything. And neither are the twins.
你的双胞胎也不会.
OK, let's get going!
咱们开始吧.
薄刀片.
Ten blade. Begin with a three-millimeter incision.
从三毫米的切口开始.
阻断血流?
- [Burke] We stop the blood flow? - To protect the brain.
为了保护大脑, 在没有血流的空间做手术 动脉瘤不会破裂
Operate in a bloodless field so the aneurysm won't rupture.
身体降温呢?
- [Burke] And cool the body? - To induce hypothermia.
降低体温.
Keeps the tissue viable until the blood is restored.
血液重新灌流之前保持组织活性
体温60华氏
Body temp is at 60 degrees.
好了, Joe.死的时间到了.
OK, Joe. Time to die.
[whirring]
血流平稳.
- [continuous beep] - Flatline.
好的.
- We've got 45 minutes, people. - Start the clock.
- 我们只有45分钟了. - 开始计时.
Got it.
[chatter]
你和Joe有什么故事?
[Derek] So what's your ''Joe'' story? Seems like everybody here has one.
看来这里每个人都有一个.
你先来.
You first.
我来这里工作前先去找Joe了
OK. l went to Joe's place the night before l started working here.
我只在市中心呆了几天.
l'd only been in town, you know, a few days.
我认识了这个女人.我喝醉了 她趁人之危
l met a woman. l got drunk and she took advantage of me.
或者是她喝醉了,我趁她之危.
Or she got drunk and l took advantage of her.
我喝醉了她没有喝酒.
l got drunk and she took... No. We were drunk. Definitely.
我们一定都醉了.
Somebody took advantage. Either way, l look at it as my initiation to Seattle.
有人趁人之危了
不管怎么样 我希望把这事看作我在西雅图的开始.
你呢?
- What about you? - Oh, l don't have one.
我没有.
l just wanted to hear yours.
我只想听听你的.
原则上说书面材料要
[George] So, technically, the paperwork just needs to be submitted
在手术开始那天中午以前上交?
by midnight of the day of the surgery to be considered?
好的.
Oh, good. Well, thank you very much. Thanks.
太谢谢你了.
谢谢.
你那里怎么样, Grey?
How you doing there, Grey?
很好.
Good. l'm good.
我很好.
- 你要是了解我了我还是很不错的. - 你不是.
You know, l'm very sweet once you get to know me.
- No, you're not. - We could be good friends.
- 我们可以做好朋友. - Alex, 永远不可能.
- Alex. Never, ever. Ever. - Why not?
- 永远. - 为什么?
Give me one reason why we could? What about you is even remotely human?
你给我一个可以的理由.
你为什总是那么难接近?
太慢了.
lt's going too slowly.
我希望Joe能挺过去.
- l hope Joe can pull through this. - He can. He will. He has to.
他能的.
他不得不.
天哪.
[Derek] Damn it. I can't get the clamp to hold.
我用这个钳子夹不住.
Give me the bipolars. l'm gonna go in at a different angle.
给我--好的, 我们要换一个角度.
还剩多少时间?
Time remaining?
- 重新灌流,快. - 17分钟.
- [Derek] lrrigation, please. - 1 7 minutes.
Shepherd,我需要8分钟让他复苏
Shepherd, l need eight minutes to get him back, to warm him up.
计时下一个17分钟.
Time to make the next 1 7 minutes count.
- 从这里进. - 你看到了?
[Derek] Right there, go in from there. See it?
See, that's why we can't do it right there.
他死了，原则上说，这是科学，这是件大事
[George] He's dead. Technically.
Which is science, and this is a huge thing.
所以我认为有的科研基金应该对这个有兴趣.
So some research foundation has to be interested.
你的意思是说你想捐Joe的身体给科学研究
So, in essence, you want to donate Joe's body to science?
至少剩下 17 分钟是
At least for the next 1 7 minutes.
- 一个私人捐助的基金. - 教育目的.
- ''Privately funded grant.'' - For educational purposes.
这是教学医院.
We're a teaching hospital. The standstill surgery qualifies.
有资格做静止手术.
l didn't peg you for the type to ignore my instructions.
你不要无视我的指挥O'Malley.
我很尊重的对您说，这个值得去做.
All due respect, sir, it's worth a shot. lt's someone's life.
这是某人的生命.
lt's always someone's life, O'Malley.
总是关于某人的生命, O'Malley.
你迷茫了.
You're hovering.
你可以走了.
- You can leave now. - OK.
[grumbles]
8分钟.
[nurse] Eight minutes.
我们现在开始复温, Shepherd.
We need to start rewarming, Shepherd.
拿着两极，谢谢
Take the bipolars, please. Thank you.
- Shepherd, 我们现在开始复温 - 拿好.
Shepherd, we need to start warming him up, now!
- 现在, 我现在就要接手他, Shepherd. - 我够不着.
- Hang on. - Now. l need it now, Shepherd.
l can't seem to get... l just can't get behind the aneurysm.
lf l could get behind the aneurysm, l could... There it is.
就这样了.
好了.
Got it. That's it.
就这样.
- Are you sure? - l'm always sure.
你确定?
我总是肯定.
[Derek] Good work, everybody. lt's all yours there, Chief.
好了，大家干得不错.
全是你的功劳，主刀.
好的，伙计们，咱们在Joe见上帝前抓住他
OK, let's grab Joe before he decides to go into the light.
开始给他复温.
Start warming him up.
松掉钳子.
Clamps are coming off.
打开泵.
Turn the pump on.
观察脑灌注压.
Watch cerebral perfusion pressures.
Keep M.A.P. Greater than 60, please.
Keep M.A.P. at greater than 60, please.
I know you're enjoying yourself, Preston.
[Richard] l know you're enjoying yourself, Preston.
It's a power kick to be the chief.
lt's a power kick to be the chief.
You're never more surrounded, never more alone.
You're never more surrounded. Never more alone.
You're everyone's father, everyone's boss and old friend.
You're everyone's father, everyone's boss, and no one's friend.
The choices we make -- clean slices, neat stitches,
Choices you make. Clean slices and neat stitches.
no emotions, no compromise, no personal life.
No emotions, no compromise, no personal life.
Richard--
- But, Richard... - l just had brain surgery.
I just had brain surgery.
I'm surrounded by fruit baskets.
l'm surrounded by fruit baskets.
The only people who've been in this room come to kiss my ass.
The only people who've been in this room come and kiss my ass.
I gave you a shot for a reason, Preston.
l gave you a shot for a reason, Preston.
You and I...
You and l, we're the same.
We're the same.
We put the job first.
That was the single most amazing surgery I have ever witnessed.
That was the single most amazing surgery l have ever witnessed.
You--you killed a man and brought him back to life.
You, you killed a man and brought him back to life.
You, like, raised the dead.
God, how does that feel? Are you rushing? Is it...
God, how does that feel? Are you rushing? ls it...
like you wouldn't believe.
Like you wouldn't believe.
Hey, do you still have those reservations? 'Cause l'm starving.
Hey, um, do you still have those reservations? 'Cause I'm starving.
Cristina...
Cristina, l think there's something we should discuss.
I think there's something we should discuss.
Yeah. Yeah, there is.
It's pretty clear.
lt's pretty clear.
It is?
lt is?
We've been fooling ourselves,
We've been fooling ourselves
to think that we can continue like this without consequences.
to think that we can continue without consequences.
Consequences?
Consequences...
We have careers to think about, reputations.
We have careers to think about.
Reputations.
We both put the job first.
And you are very focused. I respect that.
You are very focused. l respect that.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
You're welcome.
[PA] Any available IV nurse to OR two.
你想结束.
Oh, you're ending this?
我觉得最好结束的彻底一点.
l think it's best to make a clean break.
好吧.
OK.
在事情太乱之前.
Before it gets too involved. Before it gets...
- 在之前... - 乱.对，对.
Messy. Right, right. That would be bad.
那样会很糟糕
这不是针对你的.
lt's nothing personal.
进来, O'Malley.
Get in here, O'Malley.
我尽力了，我真的尽力了.
OK. l tried. l really tried.
但是最近这里有很多事情发生,
But there's a lot of stuff happening out there. Stuff l can't tell you.
我不能告诉你，不会告诉你.
Stuff l won't tell you.
都是不能想像的事情
Crazy stuff.
我想起来就做噩梦的事情.
Stuff l'm gonna have nightmares about.
但是我不准备告诉你任何一件事情 因为都是无关紧要的.
But l'm not gonna tell you about any of it.
Because it doesn't matter.
和我们都认识的喜欢的那个人无关
Not when there's a guy who we all know and love
他会因为要做手术而破产.
who's gonna be bankrupt because he needed a surgery to save his life.
- 我整天都在干这个. - O'Malley!
- l spent the whole day on it. - O'Malley...
让我说完.
Let me finish.
你错了,先生.
You're wrong, sir.
现在你可以解雇我 或者让我老老实实地遵守规矩，怎么样都可以
Now you can fire me, or bring me up on disciplinary action or whatever.
-但是我告诉你, Joe应该得到我们的... - 应该得到我们的帮助.
l'm telling you, Joe deserves...
Deserves our help. Couldn't help yourself, could you?
你控制不住，对吗?
Whether or not it'd win you any points, even from me.
不管你甚至是我要为此付出多少.
我签了你的申请.
l signed your request.
把它给Patricia. 她知道该怎么办.
Give it to Patricia, she'll know what to do.
- 看来Joe终于能保住他的酒吧了. - 谢谢你
- Joe may keep his bar after all. - Thank you, sir.
- O'Malley. - 在.
- O'Malley! - Yes?
再这样朝我吼 我就把你整得像小树枝一样顺从.
Yell at me again, and l'll snap you like a twig.
遵命.
Yes, sir.
看到了？就是一个小伤疤.
See? Just a small scar.
我的孩子呢?
And my babies?
[PA] Dr. Cole, call the OR.
你的孩子们很好.
Your babies are doing very well.
Grey医生一会就会回来给你检查.
And Dr. Grey will be back to check on you a little bit later.
事实上,我更希望Grey医生可以不再参与.
l'd prefer it if Dr. Grey were taken off the case.
为什么?有问题吗？
Why, is there a problem?
我想起了一些我不喜欢的人
Just reminds me of someone l don't like. Someone my husband likes a lot.
我丈夫喜欢的人, 特别是穿紧身内衣的.
Particularly in lingerie. You understand.
你知道.
No, no, l don't understand.
不，我不明白.
她不是和你的老公上床了吗?
Well, she's sleeping with your husband, right?
Phillips太太...
Ms. Philips, l lack Dr. Grey's class and patience
我喜欢Grey医生的层次和耐心 让我把这事情说清楚
so, let me set the record straight.
我老公没有背叛我，我背叛了他.
My husband didn't cheat on me, l cheated on him.
所以被误解的女人是
So the wronged woman here, Dr. Grey.
Grey医生.
So, l think you owe her one hell of an apology.
所以我认为你该给她道歉.
一天晚上我停了车，进了家门 有些东西不对劲.
One night l parked my car,
l unlock my front door, go inside my house, and something's different.
没有什么不对劲, 什么都没有变 但是还是...
Nothing's different, everything's the same
but yet, still, something's different.
不太对劲.
我在那里站了一会...
And l stand there for a while.
然后我知道.
And then l know.
有时候，我知道有事情要发生 在手术室也是
See, there are moments for me, you know, usually when l'm in the OR,
我能预感到下面要发生什么.
when l just know what's gonna happen next.
所以我上楼了.
So l go upstairs.
我正在大厅里, 做好心理准备.
As l walk down the hall, l try to prepare myself for what l'm gonna see
when l go into my bedroom.
我踩到了一个男人的夹克上，那夹克不是我的.
l step on a man's jacket that doesn't belong to me.
我想我全都知道了...
And everything l think l know... just shifts.
只是代替
因为虽然不是我的夹克 但是我能认出来.
Because the jacket that doesn't belong to me is a jacket that l recognize.
我知道如果我走进卧室 不仅仅会看到我的妻子不忠.
And what l know now is that when l go into my bedroom,
l'm not just gonna see that my wife is cheating on me.
会看到我的妻子在背叛我, 和Mark一起 而Mark恰恰是我最好的朋友.
l'm gonna see that my wife is cheating on me with Mark,
who happened to be my best friend.
多么俗套肮脏残酷的故事.
lt's just so pedestrian, common and dirty,
and cruel.
大部分是残酷.
Mostly just cruel.
我出来了. 我来到这里.
l left. Came out here.
-你见到了我 -我见到了你
- And you met me. - And l met you.
那我对于你来说算什么?
Well, what was l to you?
你为了熬过痛苦期而搞的女孩?
The girl you screwed to get over being screwed?
你像吹来的清风.
You were like coming up for fresh air.
好像我在堕落，你拯救了我.
lt's like l was drowning and you saved me.
这都是我想说的.
That's all l know.
还不够
lt's not enough.
[& Joe Purdy: The City]
有人说"熟能生巧".
[Meredith] They say practice makes perfect.
[engine]
原理是，你像外科大夫那样思考 你就能更像个外科大夫...
Theory is, the more you think like a surgeon
the more you become one.
你自己越中立，熟练
The better you get at remaining neutral, clinical.
切开，缝合，关上...
Cut, suture, close.
你越来越难摆脱...
And the harder it becomes to turn it off...
我早就知道了我今晚会见到你丑恶的嘴脸的.
Thought l might see your ugly mug in here tonight.
你听到好消息了没有?
Did you hear the good news?
停止像外科大夫那样思考...
...to stop thinking like a surgeon.
O'Malley!
[Alex] O'Malley!
我听说你做的事情了,担心鬼.
l heard what you did, champ.
别忘了像人类那样思考意味着什么.
[Meredith] And remember what it means to think like a human being.
医院有个规矩.
The clinic has a policy.
除非我安排一个紧急联系人 我才能确定我的职位
They wouldn't let me confirm my appointment
unless l designated an emergency contact person.
有人在那里以防万一...
Someone to be there, just in case,
and to help me home, you know, after.
能送我回家, 在那以后.
我写了你的名字.
Anyway, l put your name down.
所以我跟你说我怀孕了.
That's why l told you l'm pregnant. You're my ''person.''
- 你是我的人. - 我是?
l am?
是的,你是.
Yeah, you are.
随便你怎么说吧.
Whatever.
随便说.
他把我甩了.
He dumped me.
你认为我说这个是要让你抱吗?
You realize this constitutes hugging?
闭嘴.
Shut up.
我是你的人.
l'm your ''person.''
-==http://www.1000fr.com==- 謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译:Monica 校对:juneree